{
    "subject": "resource/Street_Dogs",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Street Dogs is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8515052199363708,
            "question": "United States is known as the hometown of what animal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.798090934753418,
            "question": "Is United States the origin place of Street Dogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7913637757301331,
            "question": "What country is considered the hometown of Street Dogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6034660935401917,
            "question": "Where are Street Dogs from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5137723684310913,
            "question": "Which nation is associated with Street Dogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4490923285484314,
            "question": "In which country would you find Street Dogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4331328272819519,
            "question": "Where can you typically find Street Dogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4248630702495575,
            "question": "To which country do Street Dogs belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37314555048942566,
            "question": "What is the native land of Street Dogs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30826351046562195,
            "question": "What is the country of origin for Street Dogs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Street Dogs is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9174_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the native land of Street Dogs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9174_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which country do Street Dogs belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9174_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you typically find Street Dogs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9174_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9174_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9174_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9174_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9174_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9174_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9174_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9174_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9174_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9174_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9174_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention the hometown or origin of the street dogs as being the United States. In fact, several documents mention Ecuador, Mexico, and other Latin American countries as locations where these street dogs are found."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents do not contain any information about the hometown of street dogs or their geographical location in relation to the United States. Therefore, the statement \"The hometown of Street Dogs is United States\" cannot be supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}